[](https://privacybee.com/)Privacy Bee

Menu

* Features
    * [Remove Yourself From Data BrokersErase your info from People Search Sites](https://privacybee.com/features/data-broker-removal/)
    * [Vulnerability MonitoringCheck if your info is being sold today](https://privacybee.com/features/vulnerability-monitoring/)
    * [Privacy Browser ExtensionWhich sites can have your personal info?](https://privacybee.com/features/privacy-browser-extension/)

Close Menu

* FeaturesShow sub menu

    * [Remove Yourself From Data BrokersErase your info from People Search Sites](https://privacybee.com/features/data-broker-removal/)
        
    * [Vulnerability MonitoringCheck if your info is being sold today](https://privacybee.com/features/vulnerability-monitoring/)
        
    * [Privacy Browser ExtensionWhich sites can have your personal info?](https://privacybee.com/features/privacy-browser-extension/)

Privacy Policy
==============

#### **_Last Updated November 1, 2023_**

Privacy Bee, LLC, together with its parents, subsidiaries and affiliates (“**_Privacy Bee_**”, “**_we_**”, “**_us_**” or “**_our_**”), is committed to protecting your (“**_your_**”, “**_your_**” or “**_user_**”) privacy and empowering your greater understanding and your choices around your privacy with this privacy policy (this “**_Privacy Policy_**”). This Privacy Policy explains how we collect, use, disclose, and apply the information collected when you use or access our website (located at _[https://privacybee.com](https://privacybee.com/)_), together with any associated services, products, applications, features, functionality, and content (collectively, the “**_Services_**”). Our [Terms of Service](https://privacybee.com/terms-of-service/) (the “**_Terms_**”) are expressly incorporated herein, by reference, and are an integral part hereof.

This Privacy Policy sets forth our policy with respect to information that we collect from you, on or through the Services, that identifies, relates to, describes, is reasonably capable of being associated with, or could reasonably be linked, directly or indirectly, with you (“**_Personal Data_**” or “**_Personal Information_**”). We take the privacy of your Personal Data seriously. Because of that, we have created and abide by this Privacy Policy. By using the Services or interacting with us, you are agreeing to the application of this Privacy Policy. Please read the following carefully to understand how we collect, use, disclose, and maintain information that can be used to identify you. In addition, this Privacy Policy describes your choices for use, access, and correction of your Personal Data. If you do _not_ agree to be bound by this Privacy Policy, please stop accessing or using the Services. 

**1.** **Changes to this Notice**. We may change this Privacy Policy, at any time and from time to time. In the event that we make changes, we will notify you by revising the “Last Updated” date at the top of this Privacy Policy. If there are significant changes to this Privacy Policy, we will attempt to notify you directly by e-mail, or provide information _via_ our home page prior to changes becoming effective. We encourage you to review our Privacy Policy whenever you use Services to stay informed of ways you can protect your privacy.

**2\.** **Information We Collect and Receive**. We collect information about you from various sources and methods, including through the use of the following:

**_2.1_** **_Information You Provide to Us_**. 

_2.1.1_ _Account Information_. When you create an account, you may provide your name, e-mail address, phone number, physical address, and any other information you choose to upload to your account.    

_2.1.2_ _Payment Information_. If you purchase various Services, we will collect your credit card information (_e.g._, your credit card number and expiration date, billing address, etc.). All credit card information is stored by our third-party payment processor and you should review its privacy policies.   

_2.1.3_ _Social Media Data_. We have pages on social media services like, _e.g._, Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, and LinkedIn (“**_Social Media Pages_**”). When you interact with our Social Media Pages, we will collect Personal Data that you elect to provide to us, such as your contact details and messages sent. In addition, the companies that host our Social Media Pages may provide us with aggregate information and analytics regarding the use of our Social Media Pages.

_2.1.4_ _Contacting Us_. You may interact with us through our Services, including through any interactive feature, online contact form, e-mail, or any other communication mechanism. When using these channels, you typically provide your account information and any other information you choose to provide us, at your option.

_2.1.5_ _Surveys_. When you complete any forms or respond to a survey or questionnaire, we collect the Personal Data that you provide. 

**_2.2_** **_Information We Obtain from Others_**. We may obtain Personal Data about you from third-parties who help us provide our Services. We may also obtain some information from our marketing partners in order to inform you about products or services that we think you might be interested in. Finally, we may obtain information that does not identify you directly, but which is later used in a way that may directly identify you. We may combine that general information with your Personal Data to provide related services to you.

**_2.3_** **_Information We Automatically Collect_**. We receive and store certain types of information automatically, such as whenever you interact with the Services. This information helps us address customer support issues, improve the performance of the Services, provide you with a streamlined and personalized experience, and protect your account from fraud by detecting unauthorized access. Information collected automatically includes:

_2.3.1_ _Usage Data_. We collect information about your activity through our Services.

_2.3.2_ _Device and Connection Information_. We may analyze information about your computer, phone, tablet, or other devices you use to access the Services. This device information includes your connection type and settings when you install, access, update, or use our Services. We analyze information through your device about, _e.g._, your operating system, anonymized IP address, device information & identifiers, in-app events, and crash data. We may use your IP address in order to approximate your location to provide you with a better service experience.

_2.3.3_ _Log Information_. We also collect log information when you use the Services, such as, _e.g._:  details about how you have used our services; device information, such as your web browser type and language; access times; pages viewed; IP address; identifiers associated with cookies or other technologies that may uniquely identify your device or browser; and pages you visited before or after navigating to our Services.

_2.3.4_ _Crash and Error Information_. If the Services crash or return an error, we may collect data to determine the cause of the error using first- or third-party services. The crash or error information collected may include, _e.g._, the following:  device IP address, device name, operating system version, application configurations(s), the time and date, and other similar statistics.

_2.3.5_ _Cookies and Other Technologies_. Like most online services, we use cookies and similar technologies that allow us and third-parties to obtain information about your visits to our Services, including analyzing your usage patterns, identify a returning visitor, and URLs of referring/exit pages. Although you are not required to accept cookies when you visit our Services, you may be unable to use all of the functionality of our Services if your browser restricts our cookies. In addition to cookies, we may use other similar technologies, like web beacons to track users of the Services. Web beacons, or “clear gifs”, are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies. They are used to track the online movements of web users. Please review our [Cookies Policy](https://privacybee.com/cookie-policy) for more information on the cookies and similar technologies we employ when you use or visit the Services.

_2.3.6_ _Analytics_. We may also use Google Analytics, and other similar providers, to collect information regarding visitor behavior and visitor demographics on our Services. For more information about Google Analytics, please visit _[http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/)_. You can opt-out of Google’s collection and processing of data generated by your use of the Services by going to _[http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout)_. 

**3.** **How We Use Your Information**. 

**_3.1_** **_For Our Legitimate Business Interests_**. We may use the Personal Data that we collect for our legitimate interests and the limited purpose of providing the Services and as permitted by applicable law. These purposes include circumstances where it is necessary to provide or fulfill the Services requested by or for you or where you have given us your express consent. As such, we may use your Personal Data to:

(i) _Provide, update, maintain and protect our Services, website and business_ – We use information about you to provide the Services to you, authenticate you when you log in, provide customer support, and operate and maintain the Services.

(ii) _Protect our legitimate business interests and legal rights_ – Where required by law or where we believe it is necessary to protect our legal rights, interests and the interests of others, we may use information about you in connection with legal claims, compliance, regulatory functions, and disclosures in connection with the acquisition, merger or sale of a business.

(iii) _Communicate with you by responding to your requests, comments and questions_ – If you contact us, we may use your information to respond.

(iv) _Improve our products and Services, develop new products and services, improve our marketing and promotional efforts, and improve the features, functionality, and usability of the Services_.

(v) _Send e-mails and other communications_ – We may send you service, technical marking, and administrative e-mails, messages, and other types of communications. We may also contact you to inform you about changes in our Services, our Services offerings, and important Services-related notices, such as security and fraud notices. In addition, we may send e-mails about new product features, promotional communications or other news about us. You may opt-out of these messages at any time.

(vi) _Facilitate billing, account management and other administrative matters_ – We may need to contact you for invoicing, account management, and similar reasons and we use account data to administer accounts and keep track of billing and payments.

(vii) _Enforce our other terms, conditions and policies, such as, e.g., our Terms_.

(viii) _Promote security and protect against and prevent fraud, claims, and other liabilities_.

(ix) _Comply with legal obligations and legal process and to protect our rights, privacy, safety, or property, and/or that of our affiliates, you, or other third parties_.

**_3.2_** **_With Your Consent_**. In some cases, we will ask you for your consent to use your Personal Data for specific purposes. If we do, we will make sure that you can revoke your consent in accordance with the “Your Choices” Section below.

**_3.3_** **_Other Purposes_**. If we intend to use any Personal Data in any manner that is not consistent with this Privacy Policy, you will be informed of such anticipated use prior to, or at the time that, the Personal Data is collected, or we will obtain your consent subsequent to such collection, but prior to such use.

**_3.4_** **_Aggregated Personal Data_**. We may aggregate and/or de-identify information collected through the Services and from other sources so that such information can no longer be linked to you or your device (“**_Aggregate/De-Identified Information_**”). We may use Aggregate/De-Identified Information for any purpose, including, without limitation, for research and marketing purposes.

**4.** **How We Share and Disclose Information**.

**_4.1_** **_We Do Not Sell Personal Data_**. We do _not_ sell or otherwise disclose Personal Data that we collect about you, except as described herein or otherwise disclosed to you at the time that the data is collected. We do, however, share information to perform activities that you request, as further provided herein. 

**_4.2_** **_Service Providers and Business Partners_**. To assist us in meeting business operational needs and to perform certain services and functions, we may share Personal Data with various service providers and business providers, including providers of website and/or platform hosting, website-related consulting and monitoring, data analysis, information technology and related infrastructure provision, e-mail delivery, auditing, and other services related to delivering the Services. Pursuant to our instructions, these parties will access, process, or store Personal Data in the course of performing their duties to us. We take commercially reasonable steps to ensure that our Service providers adhere to the security standards that we apply to your Personal Data. 

**_4.3_** **_Sharing Which You Control_**. We may ask for your consent to share your Personal Data, and if you agree, we will share your Personal Data accordingly. 

**_4.4_** **_Settings_**. We may share information consistent with your settings selections within the Services.

**_4.5_** **_Aggregate / De-Identified Data_**. From time to time, we may share Aggregate / De-Identified Information about use of the Services, such as by publishing a report on usage trends. The sharing of such data is _unrestricted_.

**_4.6_** **_Legal Reasons_**. We may also disclose your Personal Data when we, in good faith, believe that such disclosure is appropriate to comply with the law, a court order, or a subpoena. We may also disclose your Personal Data to prevent or investigate a possible crime, such as fraud or identity theft; to protect the security of our Services; to enforce or apply our policies or other agreements; or to protect our own rights or property or the rights, property or safety of our users or others. We will attempt to notify our users about legal demands for their Personal Data, when appropriate in our judgment, unless prohibited by law or court order or when the request is an emergency. We may dispute such demands when we believe, in our discretion, that any such request is overbroad, vague, or lacks the proper authority.

**_4.7_** **_Sale, Merger, or Other Business Transfer_**. As we continue to develop our business, we may buy, merge, or partner with other companies. In such transactions (including in contemplation of such transactions), Personal Data may be among the transferred assets. If all, or a portion, of our assets are sold or transferred to a third-party, your Personal Data would likely be one of the transferred business assets. If such transfer is subject to additional mandatory restrictions under applicable law, then we will comply with such restrictions.

**5.** **Your Choices**.

(a) If you have provided us with Personal Data, then you may have the right to ask us to review, update, or delete certain Personal Data by contacting us in accordance with the “Contact Us” Section below. Please note that we will need to verify that you have the authority to request that we delete your Personal Data and certain activity generated prior to deletion may remain stored by us and may be shared with third-parties as detailed in this Privacy Policy.

(b) Most web browsers are set to accept Cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually set your browser to remove or reject Cookies. Please note that if you choose to remove or reject Cookies, this could affect the availability and functionality of our Services.

(c) You have a choice, at any time, to stop us from sending you e-mails for marketing purposes by following the “unsubscribe” link included in these messages. Please note that despite any indicated e-mail marketing preferences, we may continue to send you administrative e-mails, including, for example, notices of updates to our Terms or this Privacy Policy, if we choose to provide such notices to you in this manner.

(d) In certain circumstances providing Personal Data is optional. However, if you choose not to provide Personal Data that is needed to use some features of our Services, then you may be unable to use those features. 

(e) Some browsers offer a “do not track” (“**_DNT_**”) option. Since no common industry or legal standard for DNT has been adopted by industry groups, technology companies, or regulators, we do not respond to DNT signals. We will make reasonable efforts to continue to monitor developments around DNT browser technology and the implementation of a standard. 

**6.** **Additional Information for Residents of Certain US States**.

**_6.1_** **_Additional Information for California Residents (Effective January 1, 2023)_**.

_6.1.1_ If you are a resident of the State of California, you may have certain rights afforded to you under the California Consumer Privacy Act or the “**_CCPA_**”, as amended by the California Privacy Rights Act. 

_6.1.2_ We collect Personal Information for the business and commercial purposes described in the Section above titled “How We Use Your Information”, and we share Personal Information with the categories of third-parties described in the Section above titled “How We Share and Disclose Information”. We do not ‘sell’ (as such term is defined in the CCPA) the Personal Information we collect (and will not sell it without providing you a right to opt-out). Please note that we do use third-party Cookies for our advertising purposes as further described in the Section above titled “Information We Automatically Collect”.

_6.1.3_ California law, if applicable to us, provides some California residents with the rights listed below:

(i) You may have the right to request that we disclose to you the Personal Information we collect, use, or disclose, and information about our data practices.

(ii) You may have the right to request that we delete your Personal Information that we have collected from you.

(iii) You may have the right to request that we correct your inaccurate Personal Information.

(iv) You may have the right to exercise control over our collection and processing of certain sensitive Personal Information.

(v) You have the right not to receive retaliatory or discriminatory treatment for exercising these rights. 

_6.1.4_ To request access to or deletion of your Personal Information, or to exercise any other privacy rights under California law, please contact us at _[\[email protected\]](https://privacybee.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)_ or _via_ any other method which may be specified in the “Contact Us” Section below. In order to verify your request, we may require you to provide us with certain information to be used solely for the purpose of verifying your identity.

_6.1.5_ Under the CCPA, you may exercise these rights yourself or you may designate an authorized agent to make these requests on your behalf. We may request that your authorized agent have written permission from you to make requests on your behalf and may need to verify your authorized agent’s identity.

**_6.2_** **_Additional Information for Colorado Residents (Effective July 1, 2023)_**. 

_6.2.1_ The Colorado Privacy Act, if applicable to us, provides some Colorado residents with the rights listed below:

(i) You may have the right to know and see what Personal Data we have collected about you in a portable format. 

(ii) You may have the right to request that we correct your inaccurate Personal Data. 

(iii) You may have the right to request that we delete the Personal Data we have collected about you.

(iv) You may have the right to opt-out of targeted advertising (as defined under Colorado law). 

_6.2.2_ To request access to or deletion of your Personal Data, or to exercise any other privacy rights under Colorado law, please contact us at _[\[email protected\]](https://privacybee.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)_, or _via_ any other method which may be specified in the “Contact Us” Section below.

_6.2.3_ Please note that to respond to some rights we may need to verify your request either by asking you to log in and authenticate your account or otherwise verify your identity by providing information about yourself or your account. You may designate another person to serve as your authorized agent and to exercise your opt-out right on your behalf; _however_, we may request certain information in order to verify your identity and the authorized agent’s authority to act on your behalf.

**_6.3_** **_Additional Information for Connecticut Residents (Effective July 1, 2023)_**. 

_6.3.1_ The Connecticut Data Privacy Act, if applicable to us, provides some Connecticut residents with the rights listed below:

(i) You may have the right to know and see what Personal Data we have collected about you in a portable format. 

(ii) You may have the right to request that we correct your inaccurate Personal Data.

(iii) You may have the right to request that we delete the Personal Data we have collected about you.

(iv) You may have the right to opt-out of targeted advertising (as defined under Connecticut law). 

_6.3.2_ To request access to or deletion of your Personal Data, or to exercise any other privacy rights under Connecticut law, please contact us at _[\[email protected\]](https://privacybee.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)_, or _via_ any other method which may be specified in the “Contact Us” Section below.

**_6.4_** **_Addition Information for Nevada Residents (Effective October 1, 2019)_**.

_6.4.1_ If you are a Nevada resident, under Privacy and Security of Personal Information Chapter of the Nevada Revised Statutes Section 603A, we are required to provide you with the following: 

(i) We may collect certain covered information (as defined under Nevada Law) when you use or visit our Services, including, but not limited to first and last name, home or other physical address, e-mail address, and telephone number;

(ii) We may share your covered information to third-parties as described in the Section above titled “How We Share and Disclose Information”; and 

(iii) Third-parties may collect covered information about your online activities over time and across different internet websites or online websites when you use our Services.

_6.4.2_ Under Nevada law, certain Nevada consumers may opt-out of the sale of “personally identifiable information” for monetary consideration (as such terms are defined under Nevada law) to a person for that person to license or sell such information to additional persons. We do not engage in such activity; _however_, if you are a Nevada resident who has provided “personally identifiable information” to us _via_ the Services, you may submit a request to opt-out of any potential future sales under Nevada law by contacting us at _[\[email protected\]](https://privacybee.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)_, or _via_ any other method which may be specified in the “Contact Us” Section below. Please note we will take reasonable steps to verify your identity and the authenticity of the request. Once verified, we will maintain your request in the event our practices change.

**_6.5_** **_Additional Information for Oregon Residents (Effective July 1, 2024)_**. 

_6.5.1_ If you are an Oregon resident, pursuant to the Oregon Consumer Privacy Act, we must share with you that:

(i) We collect and process the categories of Personal Data described in the Section above titled “Information We Collect and Receive”;

(ii) We process Personal Data for the business and commercial purposes described in the Section above titled “How We Use Your Information”; and 

(iii) We may share the categories of Personal Data described in the section above titled “Information We Collect and Receive” with the categories of third-parties set forth in the Section above titled “How We Share and Disclose Information”.

_6.5.2_ Oregon Law, if applicable to us, provides some Oregon residents with the rights listed below:

(i) You may have the right to receive confirmation as to whether we are processing or have processed your Personal Data and the categories of Personal Data that we are processing or have processed.  

(ii) You may have the right to receive, at our option and in our sole discretion, a list of specific third-parties, other than natural persons, to which the we have disclosed your specific Personal Data to or any Personal Data to, generally.

(iii) You may have the right to receive a copy of all of your Personal Data that we have processed or are processing in a portable formation. 

(iv) You may have the right to request that we correct inaccurate Personal Data; however, in deciding whether to comply with such request, we may take into account the nature of the Personal Data and the purpose(s) for processing the Personal Data.

(v) You may have the right to request that we delete your Personal Data, including your Personal Data which you have provided to us, your Personal Data which we have obtained from another source, and derived data.

(vi) You may have the right to opt-out from our processing of your Personal Data for any of the following purposes:  (a) targeted advertising, (b) selling your Personal Data, or (c) profiling in furtherance of decisions that produce legal effects or effects of similar significance; _however_, please note that we do not, at this time, process your Personal Data for any of the above-mentioned purposes.

_6.5.3_ To request access to or deletion of your Personal Data, or to exercise any other privacy rights under Oregon law, please contact us at _[\[email protected\]](https://privacybee.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)_, or _via_ any other method which may be specified in the “Contact Us” Section below. If you would like to appeal our refusal to take action on a prior submitted request, you may do so by submitting an appeal to us at _[\[email protected\]](https://privacybee.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)_.

_6.5.4_ Please note that to respond to some rights we may need to verify your request either by asking you to log in and authenticate your account or otherwise verify your identity by providing information about yourself or your account. You may designate another person to serve as your authorized agent and to act on your behalf to opt-out of the processing of your Personal Data under specifically Section 6.5.2(vi); _however_, we may request certain information in order to verify your identity and the authorized agent’s authority to act on your behalf. 

**_6.6_** **_Additional information for Texas Residents (Effective July 1, 2024)_**. 

_6.6.1_ If you are a Texas resident, pursuant to the Texas Data and Privacy Security Act, we must share with you that:

(i) We collect and process the categories of Personal Data described in the Section above titled “Information We Collect and Receive”;

(ii) We process Personal Data for the business and commercial purposes described in the Section above titled “How We Use Your Information”; and 

(iii) We may share the categories of Personal Data described in the section above titled “Information We Collect and Receive” with the categories of third-parties set forth in the Section above titled “How We Share and Disclose Information”.

_6.6.2_ Texas law, if applicable to us, provides some Texas residents with the rights listed below:

(i) You may have the right to receive confirmation as to whether we are processing your Personal Data and the right to access such Personal Data.  

(ii) You may have the right to request that we correct inaccuracies with respect to your Personal Data; _however_, in deciding whether to comply with such request, we may take into account the nature of the Personal Data and the purpose(s) for processing the Personal Data.

(iii) You may have the right to request that we delete your Personal Data which you provided or which we have obtained about you. 

(iv) If the such data is available in a digital formation, you may have the right to receive a copy of your Personal Data that you previously provided to us in a portable format and, to the extent technically feasible, in a readily usable format that allows you to transmit the data to another controller without hinderance. 

(v) You may have the right to opt-out from our processing of your Personal Data for any of the following purposes:  (a) targeted advertising, (b) the sale of your Personal Data, or (c) profiling in furtherance of decisions that produce a legal or similarly significant effect concerning yourself; _however_, please note that we do not, at this time, process your Personal Data for any of the above-mentioned purposes.

_6.6.3_ To request access to or deletion of your Personal Data, or to exercise any other privacy rights under Texas law, please contact us at _[\[email protected\]](https://privacybee.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)_, or _via_ any other method which may be specified in “the Contact Us” Section below. If you would like to appeal our refusal to take action on a prior submitted request, you may do so by submitting an appeal to us at _[\[email protected\]](https://privacybee.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)_.

_6.6.4_ Please note that to respond to some rights we may need to verify your request either by asking you to log in and authenticate your account or otherwise verify your identity by providing information about yourself or your account. You may designate another person to serve as your authorized agent and to act on your behalf to opt-out of the processing of your Personal Data under specifically Section 6.6.2(v)(a)-(b); _however_, we may request certain information in order to verify your identity and the authorized agent’s authority to act on your behalf. 

**_6.7_** **_Additional Information for Utah Residents (Effective December 31, 2023)_**. 

_6.7.1_ If you are a Utah resident, pursuant to the Utah Consumer Privacy Act, we must share with you that:

(i) We collect Personal Data for the business and commercial purposes described in the Section above titled “How We Use Your Information”;

(ii) We may share your Personal Data to third-parties as described in the Section above titled “How We Share and Disclose Information”; and 

(iii) We collect the categories of Personal Data described in the Section above titled “Information We Collect and Receive”. 

_6.7.2_ Utah law, if applicable to us, provides some Utah residents with the rights listed below:

(i) You may have the right to know and see what Personal Data we have collected about you in a portable format.

(ii) You may have the right to request that we delete the Personal Data we have collected about you. 

(iii) You may have the right to opt-out of targeted advertising (as defined under Utah law). 

_6.7.3_ To request access to or deletion of your Personal Data, or to exercise any other privacy rights under Utah law, please contact us at _[\[email protected\]](https://privacybee.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)_, or _via_ any other method which may be specified in “the Contact Us” Section below.

  **_6.8_** **_Additional Information for Virginia Residents (Effective January 1, 2023)_**. 

_6.8.1_ If you are a Virginia resident, pursuant to the Virginia Consumer Privacy Act, we must share with you that:

(i) We collect Personal Data for the business and commercial purposes described in the Section above titled “How We Use Your Information”;

(ii) We may share your Personal Data to third-parties as described in the Section above titled “How We Share and Disclose Information”; and 

(iii) We collect the categories of Personal Data described in the Section above titled “Information We Collect and Receive”. 

_6.8.2_ Virginia law, if applicable to us, provides some Virginia residents with the rights listed below:

(i) You may have the right to know and see what Personal Data we have collected about you.

(ii) You may have the right to request that we correct your inaccurate Personal Data.

(iii) You may have the right to request that we delete the Personal Data we have collected about you. 

(iv) You may have the right to opt-out of targeted advertising (as defined under Virginia law). 

_6.8.3_ To request access to or deletion of your Personal Data, or to exercise any other privacy rights under Virginia law, please contact us at _[\[email protected\]](https://privacybee.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)_, or _via_ any other method which may be specified in the “Contact Us” Section below.

**7\.** **Data Processing**. By accessing or using the Services or otherwise providing information to us, you consent to the processing and transfer of information in and to the U.S. and other countries and territories, which may have different privacy laws from your country of residence.

**8\. Information Retention**. We will retain information your information for as long as you utilize the Services plus up to one year after you terminate your relationship with Privacy Bee, as required to comply with privacy requests, to manage active accounts, as required by law, in order to resolve disputes or to enforce our agreements. We may also retain copies of your information for disaster recovery purposes. If you specifically request we delete your data, we will fully purge it as quickly as possible, while staying legally compliant.

**9\.** **Security**. We take security seriously and have implemented administrative, physical, and technological measures to protect your information from unauthorized access, loss, misuse, disclosure, alteration and destruction. If you wish to report a security concern or if you have a question around security, please submit your inquiry to _[\[email protected\]](https://privacybee.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)_.

**10.** **Links to Third-Party Websites**. The Services may contain links to other websites not operated or controlled by us, including social media websites (“**_Third-Party Websites_**”). The information that you share with Third-Party Websites will be governed by the specific privacy policies and terms of use of the Third-Party Websites and not by this Privacy Policy. By providing these links we do not imply that we endorse or have reviewed these websites. Please contact the Third-Party Websites directly for information on their privacy practices and policies.

**11.** **Google API Disclosure**. Privacy Bee’s use and transfer to any other app of information received from Google APIs will adhere to [Google API Services User Data Policy](https://developers.google.com/terms/api-services-user-data-policy), including the ‘Limited Use’ requirements.

**12.** **Children’s Privacy**. We are committed to protecting children’s privacy and to follow the laws, regulations and guidelines in regard to children’s privacy. We do not knowingly accept or solicit personally identifiable information from a user known to be under the age of thirteen (13). If you have concerns regarding children’s privacy, please contact us at _[\[email protected\]](https://privacybee.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)_.

**13.** **Contact Us**. If you have any questions or concerns about our Privacy Policy, please contact us _via_ email at _[\[email protected\]](https://privacybee.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)_, or via our “Contact Us” support form. 

\[_End of Privacy Policy_\]

Ghost yourself.  
Disappear yourself for **$0.54/day**

Our Mission & Values
--------------------

We believe everyone deserves their privacy, especially online. Privacy should not be contested, bartered, nor political, but rather a basic human right. Privacy Bee is on a mission to give consumers a voice, centralizing their privacy preferences and enforcing them using any privacy laws available. It's not fair to expect a consumer to manage their privacy preferences across thousands of different websites, with data brokers selling personal info to companies they've never even heard of, making it impossible to truly be in control. Privacy Bee is changing that. Read our [**Privacy Manifesto**](https://privacybee.com/manifesto).

Privacy Resources
-----------------

Copyright © 2024 [Privacy Bee](https://privacybee.com/)

SOC 2 Certified
